Happy birthday to you.
A Happy Birthday song
dedicated to the leader
of our Rongcheng Group,
-Mr. Zhou Rong.
Where's Qiqi?
-Qiqi is on the stage.
-Mr. Zhou, happy birthday
and may you have many more.
Mr. Rong,
-happy birthday!
-Happy birthday!
Thank you!
Let's party!
This is
a cake of the Eastern New City?
Yeah.
Whose idea was this?
Mr. Rong,
I had this specially made for you.
Rongcheng will definitely
take this piece of land.
Bowen,
so thoughtful of you.
Eastern New City
is indeed
a big piece of cake.
Turn the music down.
Let me tell you a joke!
Okay.
A piece of cake got lost.
Who encouraged it
to get back on the right path?
Raise your hand if you know.
Do you know?
College student?
It's me.
He said it's him.
Mr. Rong, don't keep us in suspense.
What is it?
It's...
a pig.
A pig!
Pig?
Why, Mr. Rong?
Because
it's a chonk-alate cake!
Is it not funny?
He even said it was him. Honestly.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 2]
[Sanjiangkou]
Chief Qi.
Yi'ang.
We finally got you here.
[Qi Zhenxing, Chief of
Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
Long time no see.
We'll be working together from now on.
No,
I will follow your orders.
This is Li Qian, the colleague I brought.
Hello.
Hello, Chief Qi.
Song, Song Xing.
This is the person
Ye specifically chose for you.
You just arrived here.
There are many things you don't know.
For anything,
anytime, anywhere,
you can look for him.
Chief Zhang, I'm always on call.
[Song Xing, Investigator of
Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
Hello.
Where are Ye and the others?
-Ye.
-Captain Ye said he's sick.
Deputy Captain Wang is also sick.
People in the bureau
are almost all sick.
It's the flu.
They are indeed holding a grudge.
I told you.
They all took sick leave?
No, no.
Everyone is working while sick.
The bureau has an operation these days
to support the traffic police
in checking for DUIs.
After this busy period,
we will
welcome you properly.
Chief Qi, I...
I still want to hurry up
and verify the report letter.
I don't want my temporary appointment
as the deputy chief
to cause any
unnecessary misunderstandings here.
Sure.
Unload the luggage.
Okay.
Let me do it.
Yi'ang,
the office is upstairs.
Okay.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Welcome.
[Ye Jian, Detective Captain
of Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
Ye.
Let's eat.
I'm not eating.
I have no appetite at all.
It's not that serious, is it?
Yes,
[Wang Ruijun]
considering everything,
[Detective Deputy Captain
of Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
the position of deputy chief
should be yours.
But Zhang Yi'ang is already here.
Isn't embarassing him like this
a bit much?
I'm not sulking about the position.
Do you know that Zhang Yi'ang
came here with a mission?
They say the provincial department
found a half of a report letter,
saying Chief Lu's death wasn't an accident
and that he was murdered.
He's just here to review
this case.
[Captain's Office]
It's fine if Zhang Yi'ang wants to
make a comeback,
but there's no need to use such
despicable methods.
So you assigned Song Xing, a rookie,
to him?
Giving him anyone
is a waste of police resources.
Come in.
Captain Ye.
Captain Wang is here?
Long time no see.
Caught a cold.
Yes, I've heard.
Well,
tomorrow is the 100-Day Operation.
We need to work with
the traffic police to check for DUIs.
It's an urgent task.
So Ye and I
are just making arrangements
and didn't go to pick you up.
It's fine.
It's nothing.
Sit here.
You first.
I'll sit here.
I haven't eaten this yet,
Chief Zhang.
Come, eat while it's hot.
I ate on the way.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Let's talk while eating.
Okay.
I came here on short notice.
Coming to Sanjiangkou is really like
being forced to do something
beyond my ability.
It's urgent. Mainly because it's urgent.
The provincial department
did receive a
report letter.
You guys have heard about it too.
The letter suspects that
Chief Lu's death
was not an accident.
Chief Zhang,
do you think it was an accident?
I've never doubted
your investigation conclusion.
It's mainly Director Gao.
Because he
mentioned that
he suspects
the cause of Chief Lu's death...
could be murder.
And one more thing.
It said that after Chief Lu passed away,
I
once spoke about
doubting of doubts in public.
Chief Zhang,
could it be that someone
intentionally wants to muddy
the waters?
At that time, you thought
this was
a murder?
I didn't think this was a murder.
Then why did you say that?
I just wanted to make a brief summary
of Chief Lu's life.
We are cops.
We have to doubt things every day.
But
if we have doubts,
does it mean we are right?
So we still need to
doubt our doubts.
But if we
doubt our doubts,
are we definitely right?
Not necessarily.
So we have to continue to
doubt the doubt of our doubts.
Okay.
When you read the poem,
was it only people
from the
Sanjiangkou Municipal Bureau present?
Yes.
♪ Doubt ♪
What about this?
After Chief Lu left,
the position of Deputy Chief
of Criminal Investigation
at the Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau
has been vacant for half a year.
Could some comrades internally
have some hard feelings
and wrote that report letter?
♪ Doubt ♪
I'm just talking nonsense.
Just some doubts.
So I suspect
this whistleblower
was also present
that day when I said
this sentence.
That is to say,
it might be someone from our bureau.
♪ Doubt the doubt of the doubt ♪
Doubt.
Doubt the doubt.
Doubt the doubt of the doubt.
♪ Doubt ♪
Who?
We need to investigate.
Is it me or Wang?
Not you.
Nor would it be Wang.
Because Chief Lu was your mentor.
I believe you wouldn't do this.
But the others need to be investigated.
Well, Chief Zhang,
I must correct
what you said.
Your "doubt of the doubt"
isn't only known
by the few at the meeting that day.
This sentence
has become a joke
at Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau.
Yeah.
A joke?
It's a meme?
Everyone knows it.
So,
if you want to investigate this,
you have to expand the scope.
It's not just people
from the
Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau.
It also includes
people from
the municipal public security system,
including their relatives
and friends.
All have to be investigated.
Of course.
But to tell the truth, Chief Zhang,
I doubt there really is
such a reporter.
Well, Chief Zhang,
whatever you want to investigate,
we'll cooperate.
Song's cooperation alone
is enough.
I met Song. He's quite good.
Then Chief Zhang,
anything else I can help you with?
No.
Just came to say hi.
Let's get this done quickly.
Okay.
-Okay.
-Go ahead.
The food.
You eat, Chief Zhang.
I've already eaten.
Happy birthday!
[Zhou Rong, Chairman of Rongcheng Group]
Ye still isn't here?
You know him.
He's a civil servant.
He can't make it.
Isn't he about to become
the deputy chief?
Who can stop him
from coming to have a casual meal?
[Lang Bowen, General Manager of Aotu]
What's wrong?
[Hu Jianren, Secretary of the Chairman
of Rongcheng Group]
Mr. Rong,
I heard
the province has assigned
a new police chief
of criminal investigations.
Assigned a new person?
From the province?
Where did you hear that?
It's already been publicly announced.
The new chief's name is
Zhang Yi'ang.
[Lu Yibo, General Manager
of Fenglin Night Hotel]
Zhang Yi'ang...
Zhang Yi'ang?
Have I heard this name before?
Yes.
He used to live
in Sanjiangkou.
Is it that
"doubt the doubt of the doubt"?
Yes.
What kind of wind
blew this doubtful guy over here?
Well,
I wouldn't know.
Bowen.
I have a good bottle of wine.
Come get it.
Come, Yangyang.
Ren.
Come, Ren.
Cheers.
Ye has
suffered in Sanjiangkou
for so many years.
He should have made it to the top by now.
Why is there a new person now?
I told him to build some connections
long ago,
but he just wouldn't listen.
Didn't you understand what I meant?
I was saying...
Mr. Rong,
no need to be so nervous.
It's just a new chief, isn't it?
[Ye Jian]
[I can't come. Happy birthday from afar.]
A deputy chief came
and he's immediately staying away
to avoid suspicion.
Why?
That matter was very clear.
It had absolutely nothing to do with us.
Ye said
they investigated it clearly.
No, what kind of person is Ye?
He's our bro.
That's true,
but Ye is also a cop.
Then let me put it this way,
if you broke the law,
based on emotion,
do you think Ye would let you go?
Hey,
I just don't understand.
Why can't we stay
[Lintao Motel]
without an ID?
I'm the one staying here,
not the ID card.
This is the rule.
I predict
the motel business will get harder
because these rules are getting stricter.
During the day,
we already suffered in the train aisle
for hours.
At night,
we can't just sleep on the street, right?
Even if we stay in a hotel,
the money we have
is only enough for two days.
Then we need to get money quickly.
As for getting money,
I've already figured it out.
[Chuanshi Antique Collections]
Are we selling the goods here?
But you make a good point.
Not resting well
will affect our work.
I believe in this world,
there are always people like us
[Dayou Motel]
who run hotels and don't follow the rules.
[Pingshun Motel]
[Motel]
[Peach]
Two rooms?
One.
This is a love hotel.
There's only one bed.
And it's a waterbed.
Motorized.
As long as we can sleep.
ID cards for registration.
We left in a hurry and forgot them.
Fifty extra per person without an ID.
That's a rip-off.
A hundred extra for two?
Calculated per day.
Are you staying or not?
Yes.
I told Song Xing
we'll start investigating
Chief Lu's case file today.
Song Xing said
he wouldn't be back until noon
to help us pull the files.
Aren't they supposed to fully
cooperate with us?
He said they're short-handed.
He and Captain Ye went to
the traffic police team for a meeting.
Assisting the traffic police?
Great, great, great.
Much better.
[Chuanshi Antique Collections]
♪ Burning on its own
somewhere between haziness and clarity ♪
[Peach Night Hotel]
[Chuanshi Antique Collections]
♪ In the careless detail,
he touched the color ♪
♪ The show starts getting interesting ♪
♪ I wonder who's the real onlooker here ♪
♪ Find the onlooker ♪
It's authentic, but...
[Zheng Yongbing, Independent Collector]
My friends,
do you have receipts for these?
What if we do?
What if we don't?
There was an explosion
in the provincial capital a few days ago.
Haven't you heard?
And then?
A jewelry store
was robbed by a man and a woman.
We're both men.
Yes.
I'm just afraid
they are from a questionable source.
Can you take them or not?
Take it easy.
I can.
It's not easy for us to do business.
Since you can take it,
take this too.
This stone statue...
What is it made of?
Jade.
A jade statue.
My friends,
how much do you want for it?
Chief,
the first interrogation
of the offending driver
was indeed not recorded
because the bureau's system
was being upgraded at the time.
We weren't familiar with it yet,
so it wasn't saved.
Other than the first interrogation,
the rest of the files are here.
So many.
The archive room's fire safety system
is being upgraded,
so the files are temporarily stored
in the warehouse here.
To find the files for Chief Lu's case,
you'll have to rely on yourself.
Or...
you can wait half a month.
Once the archive room is sorted out,
it'll be easier to find things.
Half a month?
Was the archive room
upgraded on short notice?
For the specifics,
you'll have to ask
Chief Qi and Captain Ye.
There are so many.
We need some manpower
to help us look.
There is definitely no manpower available.
Captain Ye took everyone in the bureau
for the DUI operation tonight.
Chen's Chicken Racks.
I'm talking about Chen's Chicken Racks.
Their chicken racks
take 40 minutes to fry.
You even have to wait in line.
I'll take you to try it another day.
If you are really busy,
you wouldn't spend two hours
at noon
just to eat some chicken racks.
How did you know
I was eating there?
I know all the good food in Sanjiangkou.
I still remember the flavors
of the few barbecue shops,
especially Chen's Chicken Racks.
Can't believe they haven't
changed the chef.
As for me,
I came to Sanjiangkou out of nowhere.
The comrades don't trust me much.
I can understand.
But if it delays work,
that won't be good, right?
I'll help you find it.
No need.
This will deepen the comrades'
misunderstanding of me.
Go do your work.
Go ahead.
Chief,
I'll look for it.
You go watch the video.
Can you do it alone?
Don't worry.
Okay.
One.
Push.
Watch your breathing.
Okay, squeeze.
Good, very good.
Okay, push.
Go, exhale.
Squeeze.
-Come on. Go on.
-Mr. Rong.
Time for your medicine.
Why only one pill?
You've been working out for a while.
You've let off enough steam.
The doctor said you have bipolar disorder.
You can't just rely on medication.
I have too many things on my mind.
Since Bowen got
the Aotu subsidiary,
he's gotten a lot of ideas.
Yibo runs Fenglin Night
and revolves around his woman every day.
That guy named Zhang got transferred back.
Nothing is going right.
Did you find out why Zhang
came back to Sanjiangkou?
No.
Should we ask Captain Ye?
Absolutely not.
When Lu was alive,
he thought Ye and I
were trading money for power.
We're just friends who grew up together.
Can't cause trouble for him.
You value relationships.
Mr. Rong,
if anything else happens,
I'll still take the blame for you.
Jianren.
We've known each other the shortest,
but in the end,
you're the most reliable.
Mr. Rong.
We've been a bit unlucky lately.
Should I hire a fengshui master?
We can spend some money.
As the saying goes,
money prevents disasters.
Let's fix the fengshui.
Okay.
You handle this.
Shuangshuang!
Come on.
You've gotten stronger recently.
Adjust this rope.
Okay, go.
One.
Two.
Watch your breathing.
Go, squeeze.
[Anzhi Road, Sanjiangkou City,
Ping'an Province]
Come in.
I've finished reading.
That fast?
Inspired by you.
If someone
wanted to make things difficult for us,
they would definitely hide the files
in the very back.
I went straight to the boxes in the back,
and found them quickly.
The driver who caused the accident
is Shen Gang.
The file clearly records that
[List of Road Traffic Accident]
as he was approaching the intersection,
he was blinded by the high beams
of an oncoming vehicle.
He didn't see
the intersection light
turn red,
so he hit Chief Lu.
The police handling the case
previously suspected
that the driver who flashed high beams
at Shen Gang
might have had an ulterior motive.
Later, it was verified
that it was indeed an accident.
But I think
it's still necessary to have Shen Gang
come over again.
They must've already asked
many questions about the driver.
Having Shen Gang come over
probably won't get us anything new.
I really want to find this driver
who turned on the high beams.
and bring him in for questioning again.
The driver with the high beams?
They already asked him too.
Ask him again.
We're just verifying.
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
Come in.
This operation against
drunk driving
is led by the Traffic Police Department,
and supported by the CID.
It's a joint operation.
I will supervise the team.
We'll act at 7:00 PM tonight.
Now, let me
assign the tasks.
My car
is fully automatic.
It's really annoying.
That day,
it was raining,
and the road was dark.
It's a flagship SUV.
Fully automatic!
It just turned the high beams on
automatically.
Maybe
it shined on that guy.
I... I already told you
about this last time.
Who knows
if it really blinded him?
Right.
If I were in his shoes,
I would definitely blame others.
But anyway,
this has nothing to do with me.
It's automatic.
I didn't even know the high beams were on.
It was only later,
when your colleagues found me,
that I knew about it.
Tell me,
why did I buy this flagship SUV?
It's even a parallel import.
Wasn't I just
looking for trouble?
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
Officers,
ask me if you need anything else.
I will definitely cooperate with
the police.
Thank you.
Take care.
Let's watch the video of the scene again.
What about him?
He doesn't give off the vibe of a killer.
"Flagship SUV."
He's good at shifting the blame.
[February 29, 2012]
At 7:00,
the operation will start on time.
Any questions?
Meeting adjourned.
Wang,
what is Zhang Yi'ang's team doing?
They seem to be reviewing
the surveillance footage from the night
of Mentor's accident.
Is the man they just brought in
the driver who hit and killed
Director Lu?
No.
He's the driver with the high beams.
I remember him.
Always bragging about his flagship SUV.
But he's definitely not the killer.
He doesn't have the vibe.
I left my laptop inside.
You go back first.
Okay.
Zhang, I'm sending you a picture.
Enlarge it and make it clear.
Archive room,
find all the cases
Director Lu was involved in
the year before he passed away.
Right now!
[The World's Jokes]
Mr. Rong.
Let me ask you a question.
What animal
is the quietest
when it gets angry?
What animal?
Take a guess.
A shark?
A tiger?
A pig?
No.
A bear.
A bear?
Why?
Because when a bear
gets angry,
[Global Jokes]
it's...
beary quiet.
Funny.
The doctor said
that laughing more
is good for your health.
What were you going to say?
Mr. Rong, I've asked around.
The newcomer Zhang Yi'ang
used to work in the Veteran Cadre Bureau
of the provincial department.
Veteran Cadre Bureau?
That's quite unexpected.
But...
How could someone
from the Veteran Cadre Bureau
come to Sanjiangkou
to be the deputy chief?
Maybe he sucked up
to some old leader.
That's not funny.
Don't be vulgar.
Rumor has it
that the provincial department
received a report letter.
What report letter?
Who did they report?
I'm not sure.
Only insiders know.
A report letter.
Who would they report?
Mr. Rong,
if you really want
to put your mind at ease,
I suggest
we still need to ask Captain Ye.
Even if it's indirect,
even if it's just having a meal...
Feel out his attitude.
[The World's Jokes]
[Criminal Investigation File]
It's unrelated.
Why would he do this?
Captain Ye.
What is it?
I carefully studied
the traffic violation records
from the last three months.
There were 12 cases of drunk driving,
23 cases of driving after drinking,
and 5 cases of driving without a license.
There were also unlicensed vehicles
and overloading.
What are you trying to say?
I think
our joint
city-wide DUI operation
with the traffic police brigade
should expand the key areas
to not only national
and provincial highways,
but also key rural roads.
The time frame should also be extended
from midnight to morning.
We need to check not only night drinking
but also morning drinking.
Do you know how much manpower
this kind of check would require?
Use your brain!
I'm just
thinking for the joint operation.
Chief Zhang.
Ye.
I'm feeling
a bit unwell.
I'll leave tonight's DUI check
to you.
Is it the flu?
The flu.
Ye,
you're still more familiar
with the bureau's work.
We're here just to investigate
the report letter.
Any new discoveries in Chief Lu's case?
Not yet.
Still investigating.
So you see,
we can't spare the time.
Won't you help me out with this,
Chief Zhang?
I didn't say I wouldn't help.
Thank you.
I didn't say I would either.
Captain Ye.
Going to eat?
The joint operation is at 7:00 tonight.
Don't be late.
Okay.
We must meet tonight.
I just want to ask you one question.
The night Lu Zheng had his accident,
where were you?
The comrades want to see
if I'm qualified to be the chief.
They're making things more difficult
to test my qualifications
to be the chief.
I must withstand this test.
Can you withstand it?
Chief!
I heard that the operation tonight
will be in your charge.
I have a small suggestion.
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau
DUI 100-Day Operation Plan]
This is so detailed.
You came prepared.
We'll execute according to this plan.
Yes.
[Loyalty]
Then let me emphasize two points.
One,
ideologically,
we must attach great importance to it.
We must always keep in mind
our mission.
At the same time,
put down your burdens
and travel light.
Empty your minds.
Two,
disciplinarily,
we must absolutely obey commands.
However,
we must not forget to be flexible.
A general in the field
is not bound by orders from the sovereign.
Everyone, please pay attention to safety.
That's it.
Let's go!
[Public Security]
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
[Police]
Come this way.
Here, blow.
That's enough.
[Police]
Blow.
Okay, go.
Come on, blow.
Blow.